Kenneth Sinder

LinkedIn: ksinder · GitHub: kennethsinder

Summary

Software engineer with >6 years of experience. Passionate about API design and debugging.

Languages: Python, Ruby, JavaScript, C#, PHP, HTML, C++, C, TypeScript, Java, Scala, OCaml. **Web**: REST, Laravel, Flask, React, ASP.NET MVC, Django, Angular, Vue, Ember.js, jQuery, CSS.

Experience

Software Engineer · **Notion** · *San Francisco*, CA · Dec 2024 – present

• Working on the foundations and implementation of our Public API.

Software Engineer · **Stripe** · South San Francisco, CA · June 2020 - Nov 2024

- Built new business models and enterprise contract management support into Stripe Billing.
- Designed and implemented Stripe Tax integration for subscriptions and invoices.
- Evolving and maintaining high-volume global recurring revenue APIs and infrastructure.

Systems and Infrastructure Engineer Intern · LinkedIn · Sunnyvale, CA · Fall 2019

- Designed API for storing metadata for third-party → LinkedIn HDFS big data ingestion.
- Created customizable web UI internal tool for collecting Q&A answers and metadata.
 - Reduced time to onboard new data integrations from months to days.

Engineering Intern · **Stripe** · *San Francisco*, CA · Winter 2019

Software Engineering Intern · **Wish** · *San Francisco*, *CA* · Summer 2018

Full-Stack Software Developer · Hootsuite · Vancouver, Canada · Fall 2017

Software Developer · Tangam Systems · Waterloo, Canada · Winter 2017

Software Developer · **CANARIE** · Ottawa, Canada · Summer 2016

Education

Bachelor of Software Engineering, University of Waterloo · Canada · 2015 – 2020

- Attained Dean's Honours List every term for consistently averaging in top 10%.
- Learned C, C++, Scala, OCaml, and Assembly (MIPS/ARM) in regular and enriched courses.